{
    "subject": "resource/Sakyo_Komatsu",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Osaka",
    "human_readable": "Sakyo Komatsu was born in Osaka.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9143039584159851,
            "question": "Where was Sakyo Komatsu born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41961100697517395,
            "question": "What is Sakyo Komatsu best known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24733342230319977,
            "question": "What impact has Sakyo Komatsu had on Japanese literature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21678435802459717,
            "question": "Are there any notable recurring themes in Sakyo Komatsu's works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1750134825706482,
            "question": "What is the name of one of Sakyo Komatsu's most famous novels?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16729770600795746,
            "question": "Has Sakyo Komatsu's work been translated into other languages?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16167008876800537,
            "question": "Has Sakyo Komatsu won any awards for his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14760062098503113,
            "question": "Has Sakyo Komatsu written any non-fiction works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1356516033411026,
            "question": "Can you name a popular film adaptation of one of Sakyo Komatsu's novels?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1326674073934555,
            "question": "What genre of writing does Sakyo Komatsu primarily focus on?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sakyo Komatsu was born in Osaka.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8411_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a popular film adaptation of one of Sakyo Komatsu's novels?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8411_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Sakyo Komatsu written any non-fiction works?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8411_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Sakyo Komatsu won any awards for his work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8411_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8411_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8411_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8411_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8411_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8411_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8411_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8411_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8411_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8411_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8411_69.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is based on the information provided in multiple documents, which consistently mention that Sakyo Komatsu was born in Osaka."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}